Thank you for watching!
Thanks for your work
Please do...
Hallo! Ste. This time we have with us Morning Musume.' 23's Rio Sakurai and Kisaki Emoto from Juice- Juice.
These two will be presenting this time, so please stay with me until the end.
Project 2023 Spring City Circuit has come to an end.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Morning Musume。 23 will be performing in Okinawa on July 8, so please look forward to seeing them there as well.
Juice- Juice was given the opportunity to do the shuffle unit corner on this tour,
It was a very fresh and rare experience for Juice-Juice, and I think it was a very good memory for me.
I had a chance to see them at the Budokan.
It was really?
It was really wonderful.
Thank you very much.
Morning Musume。 23 has quite a gap in costumes for this spring tour,
There was a long white dress costume and a camouflage pattern costume,
I think you could feel the gap between the two outfits during the concert.
It was like a white dress, wasn't it?
Everyone looked like princesses,
They were so cool and cute,
I thought it was wonderful.
Thank you very much. I'm so happy.
Project 2023 SUMMER CITY CIRCUIT tour will start on July 15.
Yes, that's right. Since it will be an encore performance of the spring tour, do you have any particular point you would like the audience to see?
Yes, I do. I think there are probably some things that I wanted to see that I didn't get to see on the spring tour,
I think you will be able to see all of them on the summer tour.
Yes, I hope you enjoy the 10th anniversary of Juice-Juice.
We will do our best for the summer tour as well.
Now, please take a look at this video first.
Here you go!
You can come back check back check 1 2 1 2
Wow wow wow
Yo everybody do it again
Come on come on
I'm gonna eat ya!
What's up my baby?
Yeah!
Why do you love me?
Get up my baby!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Girizonindle, Japan
The rice is good, Japanese
Drink your tea, drink your tea, drink your sake
Sake.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
You're good with water.
Come on!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
But it's Japan
Feelin' great Hello!
Yeah!
Super absolutely right here.
Smile!
All the beauties
Japanese
Oh Yeah!
How do you like this Japan?
People from all over the world
I'm sure you'll say it again, yeah.
Bad bitch, uh...
What's up baby?
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Why do you love me?
Yeah yeah yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm going back to Nitori Jim's
Yeah yeah yeah
I felt the earth, jackalbeats
How do I keep myself up?
People all over the world
You're gonna love it. I'm not good at it.
How do I keep myself up?
The blacks.
Let's get prettier and prettier
Ah Ah Like this Ah
Yeah Yeah Ah
Come on!
How do I keep myself up?
People all over the world
You're gonna love it. I'm not good at it.
How do I keep myself up?
The blacks.
Come back here and tell me where you're from.
How do I keep myself up?
People from all over the world
I'm glad you said what you wanted to say
How do I keep myself up?
That's why, guys.That's why, guys.
I'm sure they'll start feeling sorry for you again.
Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah
We like crying sunplaza
Morning Musume。 23's Rio Sakurai and
Kisaki Emata of Chus Chus, and Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume'23 and Kisaki Emata of Chus Chus. Station.
From here, we would like to talk a little about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so let's answer them quickly and without thinking too much.
Yes, I will.
Pride Bright is included in the new single to be released on July 12.
What was your first impression when you received the song?
It's ear catching.
This will be your third single release since joining the band,
What did you consciously work on during the recording process?
Creating my voice.
It has been almost two years since I joined Juice-Juice.
Looking back on the past two years, what do you want to praise yourself for?
Mental growth.
Ms. Emada, please give me some tips on how to arrange my hair.
Apply oil thoroughly.
Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year.
If you could perform alone, which song would you like to perform?
Berryz KOBO's "I Can't Live Without You".
Thank you very much.
My first impression when I received the song "Pride Bright" was that it would be a song that would stick in my ears,
I myself have been listening to many new songs.
I have been listening to a lot of new songs, and I thought it was the kind of tune that I would want to listen to over and over again.
That's right. I also listened to many of the songs when I first received the sound recordings,
Even after listening to it two or three times, I could still hum the tune,
The melody and lyrics are easy to sing and catch your ear,
It is also an easy song to sing with a melody and lyrics that are easy on the ears.
I will listen to it a lot in the future.
Thank you very much.
I had my hair arranged by Mr. Ebata for the winter tour and other occasions,
He did it for me twice,
I have had my hair arranged twice by Mr. Ebata,
I posted a picture of it on my blog.
It was very well received,
That's how it turned out.
I wanted to arrange my hair as well as Ms. Ebata did,
I also thought that I should apply hair oil often,
That's right.
If you don't apply anything, it doesn't look cohesive.
But I am also the worst at arranging hair in Juice-Juice.
Really?
I can't do it for myself at all,
I can only curl my hair for others,
I can only curl my hair for other people, but I really can't curl my hair at all,
But I would like to curl my hair a lot from now on.
I have the impression that everyone at Juice-Juice is good at arranging hair,
I'd love to have the chance to do so in the future.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
Questions for Rio Sakurai will be asked after the VTR.
Hello! STE.
Love you, promising us!
In the first place, earth is a heteronomous meat cannibal
Feel proud of yourself and use it.
Maine Eva Ai no Beast
Now on sale
I love you I'm sorry I doubted you
I love you actually lover of a lover
I wanted to love you I couldn't love you
I don't kiss okay
I didn't even have you
Pride Bright July 12 on sale
Is it the summer or a dream?
Slightly Emotionally Unstable
Slightly Emotionally Unstable July 26 on sale
Hallo! Sta.
Next, I would like to ask Rio Sakurai a question.
Your first photo book, Rio 17, was released on June 29.
What made you realize that you have this side of yourself?
Her lively expression when she is with animals.
What are you consciously trying to change since the first junior member joined the group?
Talk a lot.
I talk a lot. Ste is being distributed on June 21.
Ambitious Ambitious! was released.
In one word, how do you feel when you perform this song?
Passionate
What hairstyle would you like to try in the future?
I would like to have bangs someday.
What is your favorite instrumental song from Hello!
Morning Musume。 19's Life Blues
Thank you very much.
Well, I had five questions for you.
The one that caught my attention was
I think your first photo book will be released on June 29.
I was wondering if you could tell us how you worked hard on it or something like that.
I'd like to ask you something else that I'm curious about.
Well, I had a lot of opportunities to wear this costume.
There were so many different scenes.
I hope I could change my expression a lot.
Among them, I went to a farm and took pictures with animals.
I went to a farm and took pictures with animals.
I held a little goat in my arms.
or walking with a pony.
It was wonderful!
I don't really look at my own facial expressions when I'm with animals
I don't look at it objectively.I don't look at it very objectively.
I thought you were very lively.
I made a conscious effort to improve my facial expressions and clothes.
I made a conscious effort to make my expressions and clothes look good.
I saw a picture of you dressed like a tennis player.
I thought it was really cute.
Thank you very much.
There's one more thing I wanted to ask.
What kind of hairstyle do you want to have in the future? I asked her.
She said she wanted to get bangs.
I was also wondering about your hair color.
I see.
My hair color is milk tea.
So I was wondering if I could get a lighter or milk tea-colored hair color.
I'd like to dye my hair a lighter color, like a milk tea color with dust.
I would like to dye my hair that color.
I haven't had bangs for a long time.
I'd like to make them.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm so happy! Thank you very much.
Hallo! Ste. It will continue after this!
I'm Kimiyami Natsuyaki.
This is Yumi Kasai from Tsubaki Factory!
I will do my best for Kansai!
Well, teacher, what would you like to make today?
I'd like to make a cold shabu-shabu salad.
It looks like summer. It's so cool.
It's getting hotter and hotter.
I like the sound.
I'm getting on board.
With a little bit of hand crumpling
We're off to a good start.
What would you like to start with this time?
Yes, now it's time to shabu-shabu the meat.
We have sugar and alcohol.
Please put them in.
Don't throw away the water you used to boil the noodles.
The water that you didn't throw away.
Don't boil the water.
There should be a slight mass of water.
Take a glance at it.
If it's hard to take out, put the whole two sheets
In the middle of it.
If you put them in from this side as much as possible
When you get to this point, put them in in order from this side
When the color changes, move it to the pad.
Here is the point of Miyamizu
Do not soak the meat in cold water.
Today, right?
What do you think is the part?
There are various kinds of loin and something like that.
Do you understand?
Pork is belly.
It's a belly.
It's a little oily.
I chose the one with less oil.
But if you soak it in cold water...
This oil hardens when soaked in cold water.
It's true, it turns white.
The texture is not good.
And it's a little sticky.
Open it in a place like this.
Leave it at room temperature.
Then you can eat it smoothly.
Soak the vegetables in cold water, but don't soak the meat.
but don't soak the meat.
One thing you have to be careful about...
If you use raw meat, just use chopsticks.
When you bring it up here, just dip it here for a second.
It's fine if you do it for a couple of seconds.
It's a little bit...
It's a little scary, isn't it?
I never get tired of eating meat.
I know.
You can keep eating it at the market.
One thing you can do is not throw away the water after boiling.
If you're good at it.
I want to make this soup again.
The oil from the meat...
Remove all the scum.
Cut up the green onions.
And soy sauce.
You don't waste it, do you?
I don't.
It's a waste.
I personally enjoy this process the most.
Because I love meat.
That's absolutely why.
I think it's because I love meat.
Now that the meat is boiled, it's time for toppings and serving.
If it gets a little sticky, just give it a dab with water like this.
And then open it up again, and you're good to go.
Put about half of the noodles in the bowl.
I think it's better if it's a little bit thicker.
Serve it up!
Not this Dawn.
It's like a tower.
Let's make it thicker and thicker.
Let's pile up a lot of things.
It's okay to make a big pile.
Like this?It's like this?
Let's get to the first meat!
Let's get to the meat!
The first meat!
It's very appetizing, but with all these vegetables and meat on top...
And more!
The second stage.
The last step is to put as much green as possible on top.
I see.
It's blooming.
It bloomed.
A little bit like this.
It's blooming a little bit.
It's blooming.
And the tomatoes are kind of scattered around.
It looks a little like paprika.
Yes, it does.
Looks delicious.
Is everything all right?
Yes, it's fine.
Is it droopy? Meat.
It's fine.
It's done.
Thank you very much for the meal.
The shabu-shabu salad is ready.
What do you think, Yumi?
The meat looks so sparkling, and the vegetables are so colorful and beautiful.
I think the vegetables are also very colorful and beautiful.
Let's try it now!
Bon appétit!
Here you go.
Stop!
That's enough.
It'll change the taste, so half a portion.
That's about right.
You're free to do as you please.
I'm fine with the original.
Bon appétit.
It's delicious.
Is it good?
The meat is so tender.
The doctor said it's very smooth.
It has that kind of texture.
But I thought it would be more refreshing if I ate the nourishing face with the meat.
That's nice.
The doctor prepared sesame seeds today.
Please try the sesame sauce!
The sesame sauce is absolutely delicious.
It's waiting for you there.
That thing at the bottom.
My favorite noodles.
Yes, there are noodles in there.
I didn't see the noodles.
That's right.
Please eat the noodles, too!
You can't see them yet.
Here we go.
It's so right!
Sesame sauce is an absolute perfect match.
You can't go wrong with it.
Take out the noodles, take them out from the bottom, and eat them with the meat.
Looks delicious!
We're hungry, aren't we?
I want some.
The dressing and the noodles go so well together.
It's so refreshing.
It's so light and refreshing.
It's perfect for summer.
Also, it's a little different from somen noodles.
If you're tired of eating somen noodles...
I think this dressing goes really well with ramen noodles.
So Yumi, how did you like being on Hello Kitchen this time?
Was it your first time?
It was my first time.
I didn't know how to cut it at all.
But you taught me how to do it.
He also taught me some tricks.
I was able to learn something today that I would never have known on my own.
I want to become a professional knife chef.
I want to become a professional with knives.
I want to do my best
In fact, I'll do my best.
Yes, please do your best!
So thank you again, Yumichan-sensei!
Thank you very much!
That's all for Hello Kitchen!
Bye bye!
It looked delicious!
Yes, the Reishabu salad looked really good.
Do you have a favorite salad?
Well, I eat choregui salad quite often.
Looks delicious!
Yes, Mr. Ebata, I think you appeared in this corner before.
How about after that?
Well, I made fluffy pancakes.
After that, my brother wanted to try them.
So I made it for him and he ate it.
Wow, that's very funny.
Do you do any cooking, Rio Sakurai?
I rarely have a chance to cook.
But I really like to make a bowl of rice.But I really like rice bowl dishes.
It's delicious, isn't it?
So if I can make tokidon or something like that by myself...
I'm thinking that would be great.
Great. Well, if you make some...
I'll look forward to your blog about how you made it.
I'll post it.
Thank you very much.
Hello! Sta!
Next is the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart!
There are many songs in Hello! Project has many songs.
Project has a lot of songs, and we would like to present our favorite part of the lyrics of some of them.
Project has many songs, and we would like to present our favorite lyrics.
Yes, I'm Morning Musume。
I really like the lyrics of "Mikan" by Morning Musume。 I really like the lyrics of "Mikan" by Morning Musume。
The lyrics, "You should love everyone, you only live once," are really encouraging and I also like the lyrics of "Mikan" by Morning Musume.
It really encourages me.
It makes me feel like I can do it.
It's the kind of lyrics that make you determined to do it once in your life.
What do you think, Ms. Shibata?
Well, I like the song "Choice and Chance" by Juice-Juice.
Choice and Chance by Juice-Juice.
I really like the lyric "I'd rather have regrets for having done something than regrets for not doing something" in the song "Choice and Chance" by Juice-Juice.
I'm trying to do my best now in the spirit of giving it a try.
I really like the lyrics of that song.
Thank you very much.
Now please watch the VTR.
Please watch the VTR.
Presentation of lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we will present lyrics from Hello! Project's songs that have touched our hearts and talk about their charms.
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project's songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Okamura Minami, will be presenting!
Ta-da!
I'm going to jump over my own boredom...
Nobishiro Beyond the World
This is a song from BEYOND THE WORLD!
This is just one word before the last chorus,
I really like this song "Nobishiro Beyond the World" because all the lyrics resonate with me,
I think it's wonderful that the visual object of the song is not other people or my past self, but my present self,
No matter what time of day I listen to it, or when I'm feeling a little down, it makes me want to do my best,
I can listen to it at any time, even when I'm feeling a little down, and it makes me want to do my best,
When I listen to this song when I'm depressed and feel like I haven't grown at all, it makes me want to do my best,
When I listen to this song when I am depressed and feel that I have not grown at all, I sometimes think that maybe I have grown more than I did a little while ago, that maybe I am better than I was yesterday,
It is a lyric that I remember very well because it made me realize that I had not grown at all.
When I feel like I haven't grown, it's because I'm bored with myself.
When you want to become a different person, you think that way,
I wonder what it is,
I feel like I'm tired of being exactly the way I am.
I feel like I'm tired, exactly like that.
It's a song that tells me that I can't keep growing forever.
I really like the lyrics of this song, and I hope it will be shared with many people.
That was the lyrics presentation that touched my heart.
Hallo! STE
Morning Musume。 23's Rio Sakurai and Juice-Juice's Kisaki Emada will be presenting the lyrics of the song on "Halo! STE!
I would like to talk about Nippon Budokan from now on,
Morning Musume。 23 will be held next Monday, June 26th.
Morning Musume。 23 25th Anniversary Concert Tour Grad Quarter Century at Nippon Budokan.
This will be the second time for me to perform at Nippon Budokan since I joined the group,
The last time was last December,
It had not been that long since I joined the band,
I was just barely able to get up on stage and perform, so this time, I am going to perform at the Nippon Budokan,
This time, six months have passed since our last performance at Nippon Budokan,
So this time, six months after our last performance at the Nippon Budokan, I hope to perform with an awareness of the venue and the importance of delivering the message to the audience.
I joined Girigiri on June 26.
So, this is the one year anniversary of my joining the group,
I am preparing for the event so that everyone can see the culmination of all my efforts up to this point.
I am looking forward to seeing it.
Please look forward to it. Thank you very much.
As for Juice-Juice, we finished the Nippon Budokan concert one step ahead of the others,
I was really excited because I had to speak out, and all the members were too excited,
The members were also too excited.
I met a new member, Mifu Kawashima, for the first time, and we talked a lot backstage and so on.
It was a lot of fun.
Yes, it was. Morning Musume。 Haruka Inoue and Ayako Yume-Ikeda have joined Morning Musume,
We are planning to unveil them next Monday, June 26, at the Nippon Budokan,
Please look forward to their debut next Monday, June 26, at the Nippon Budokan.
Please look forward to it as well.
Thank you for watching.
But I'm sure you'll be fine.
But it's going to be okay.
It's going to be okay.
Whenever I feel anxious
To the words I told myself
Let's take a walk, hang out for a bit
Let's walk, shoulder to shoulder, talking nonsense
Talking lightens the heart
Silhouettes stretching into the setting sun
Just a ring bed ahead
I still can't say with a smile that I've missed you
Every day is just something
Don't stop what you can't do
One day later
Dreams
I have room to grow
I haven't taken anything away from you yet
It's just beginning
Hey baby
Let's smile
♪ And when you're down
And they'll laugh at usThey laugh at me.
There's no such thing as a dark song
There's no such thing as us
I am what I think I am
I'm what you think I am
I can't see it in myself
Personality and charm
That's the first time you've ever said that to me
You're the only one
You'll find yourself smiling again
You have room to grow
You have room to grow.
You're the kind of person who makes people feel like they can do something
You make me feel like I can do something
I have room for growth.
I have room to grow
Spread your wings
With you flapping your wings
Beyond the heart
I'll protect you
TATARA TATARA
When I look back, I see the me of that day in the distance
The tears that wouldn't stop will one day turn into smiles
Don't worry, I'm sure this road stretches into the future
The road we live on, one that never stops
Free, forever, every day
I'll leap over the self I've set for tomorrow
No peace, syndrome
Nothing's over yet.
It's just beginning
No big deal
No big deal Alcohol
Spread your wings
With you flapping your wings
No big deal
Let's fall in love
I've got nothing
Nothing yet
It's not over.
See you later
To the dream again
Let's fly away to our dreams
Walk to the end of your mind
The end of the wide land with you
Scrolling up!
Oh Yeah Oh Yeah
I'm flapping my wings
Kick up, kick up, kick up, kick up, kick up
Kick Up, Kick Up, Kick Up, Kick Up
Oh, yeah
Thank you!
Thank you for watching
Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。 23's Rio Sakurai and
Saki Ibaraki of Juice-Juice presents "Halo! Ste.
It's time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
On Monday, June 26th, Morning Musume。 23 25th Anniversary Concert Tour
Grad Quarter Century at Nippon Budokan.
As I mentioned earlier,
This will be my second concert at Nippon Budokan since I joined the group,
I will do my best and put a lot of energy into it,
Please look forward to it.
Please look forward to it. 23 Rio Sakurai's first photo book "Rio 17 years old" will be released on Thursday, June 29.
Rio Sakurai's first photo book will be released on Thursday, June 29th.
June 29th is the one year anniversary of my joining Morning Musume,
I am very happy to be able to release it on June 29th.
As the title says, you will be able to see a lot of the 17-year-old me in this book,
Please look forward to it.
Juice-Juice will be releasing a new album on July 12.
Pride Bright Funky Flashing" will be released as a double A-side single.
Both songs are completely different,
Pride Bright is very cool,
Funky Flashing is a refreshing song,
I hope you can feel the gap between the two songs.
We will be participating in the Rock in JAPAN Festival 2023 on August 13.
Project, Morning Musume. 23, Angulum, Juice Juice, and Airi Suzuki from Hello!
Project, Morning Musume, Angelem, Juice- Juice, and Airi Suzuki will participate.
This will be my first time participating in the festival, so I am a little nervous,
I'm a little nervous because it's my first time to participate, but I'm going to do my best with all my energy.
The "Halo! Project members will appear on the channel.
Project members. New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
This time I'll be talking with Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。 23's Rio Sakurai and
23 and Kisaki Emoto of Juice-Juice.
Farewell!
Thank you for watching.